

ABOUT ME

I'm an impact-driven and curious product designer with experience in e-commerce and SaaS industry. My passion lies in designing solutions that leave a lasting, postive impact. I strive to tackle any problem with critical thinking and a positive attitude.

TECH SKILLS

DESIGN

Miro

TOOLS
Figma HTML/CSS
Figjam Javascript/jQuery
Adobe CC Google Analytics
Principle Git/GitHub
Overflow Zeplin

Hotjar

COMPETENCIES

Visual Design Interface Design Interaction Design Experience Design Wireframing Prototyping Design System
Design Heuristics
User Research
User Interview
Usability Testing
Data Analysis

FRONTEND DEV

EDUCATION

SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY

B/A - Interactive Arts + Technology Design Concentration

Graduated with Distinction and Co-op Education Award 2014 - 2019

ACHIEVEMENTS

DEAN'S HONOR ROLL

FALL 2014

Awarded to students for achieving a 3.50 (out of 4.33) or higher GPA.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Designer / Shopee

JUL - NOV 2022

- Designed intuitive solutions to improve the seller centre and buyer marketplace experience based on the existing regional design system.
- Communicated with cross functional teams to develop solutions, receive feedback, and manage multiple projects in a fast-paced environment.

Senior Product Designer / Tokoplas

SEP 2020 - JUN 2022

- Worked closely with management and engineers to redefine the user experience of the e-commerce website, seller portal, and mobile apps.
- Led the design efforts of the new website and seller portal as well as creating design system, mockups, and prototypes for development.

UI/UX Designer / Zaui Software

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

- Collaborated with engineers and product experts to design flows and features for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.
- Developed wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and interactive prototypes for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.

Digital Designer / PayByPhone

OCT 2018 - APR 2019

- Redefined the user experience and redesigned the interface of the new parking operators (B2B) and careers pages.
- Produced marketing materials for print and digital such as promotional banners, posters, postcards, display ads, and social media graphics.

UI/UX Designer / BSTRO

MAY - SEP 2018

- Collaborated with designers in an agency environment to design digital experiences for J&J, Chef Software, and San Francisco Marathon.
- Day-to-day included creative concepting, competitive analysis, sitemap drafting, wireframing, mockups design, and prototyping.

UI/UX Designer / Buzzlt Inc.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

- Worked collaboratively with a product manager and a developer in redesigning Buzzlt's website and mobile apps in a startup environment.
- Overhauled the visual design and user experience of the entire Android & iOS app by producing 50+ sets of end to end mockups.